Guide to the National Law Center records, 1865-2005 RG0014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Law alumni photographs, 1921-1989; RG0014 Series 13; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 9, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 13, Box 12, Box 11, Box 10, Box 15, Box 14, Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5)
  - Jim Ziglar, Barron,Sehade, Milo Price, 06/16/1980 (Box 3, Folder 18.1)
    Phoenix
  - Caplan, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.2)
  - A group chatting over dinner, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.3)
    Hawaii, Unidentified
  - President Elliot addressing an audience, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.4)
  - J. Roger Detiveiler, Dean Jerome Barron, William L. Harnton, Gary G. Bullis, 09/17/1979 (Box 3, Folder 18.5)
    Comstrich Hotel, Reno, Nivada
  - Invitees at a reception, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.6)
  - Prof. Ralph Nash with David Warner, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.7)
  - Pres. Elliot chatting with Bruce F.Fein and Mrs.Fein at a reception, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.8)
  - GWLA Luncheon, Annual Meeting California, 09/18/1979 (Box 3, Folder 18.9)
    Reid R. Briggs and Dean Jerome A. BarronUnidentified
  - GWLA Breakfast at the Broadmoar Hotel,Colorado Bar Association, 09/29/1979 (Box 3, Folder 18.1)
    George H. Whitemob, Batty A. Thompson,Judge Donald E.Campbell, Judge William DoyleUnidentified
  - Dean Jerome A. Barron and Charles T. Manatt, 09/17/1979 (Box 3, Folder 18.11)
    Los Angeles, Unidentified
  - A couple in a reception, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.12)
  - GWLA Luncheon, State Bar of California, 09/18/1979 (Box 3, Folder 18.13)
    Judge Lenne Schreider, Dean Jerome A. Barron,Judge Lucy K. McCabe
  - Jacob A. Stein and Michael Cramer at a reception, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.14)
  - Judge Joyce Hens Green and two other individuals chatting at a reception, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.15)
  - Albert Ginsberg and two other individuals chatting at a reception, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.16)
  - Three men in a reception, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.17)
  - GW Law Assoc. Luncheon, Kansas Bar Assoc., 05/14/1979 (Box 3, Folder 18.18)
    [l to r] J. Elwood Slover, Lee Thompson, Ellis Bever, Brain E. Sullivan, Arthur C. Hodgson, Roger H. Morse, Rovert W. Wise, Frank Melone, Joseph W. Kennedy
  - William A. Oliver being honored at an event, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.19)
  - Judge Joyce Hens Green and Jake Stein, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.2)
  - Mary Stallings Coleman, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.21)
  - Larry Careso, Ed Patts, and others chatting, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.22)
  - Robert Park honoring a certificate to Rosalyn Blake Bell, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.23)
  - Shannon speaking at a Brunch, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.24)
  - State Bar of Texas at the, 06/13/1980 (Box 3, Folder 18.25)
    Judge Garner, Jack Goldstein, and Gookwin, Unidentified
  - Tricia Graham, Robert C. Burk Hayder, and others chatting at a reception, undated (Box 3, Folder 18.26)
  - James P. Chandler, undated (Box 3, Folder 19.1)
  - Law Alumni Dinner for Dean Jerome A. Barron, Philadelphia PA, 03/20/1980 (Box 3, Folder 19.2)
    Jay J. Bomze, Alan S. Nadel, Dean Jerome A. Barron, Stanley H. Cohen
  - General Alumni meeting, Dallax Texas, 02/11/1980 (Box 3, Folder 19.3)
    George Goodwin, Frances Goodwin
  - GW Law Ass. Annual Luncheon, New York Bar Association, N.Y.Hilton, 01/23/1980 (Box 3, Folder 19.4)
    Dr. Seymour Alpert, D. Jacob Burns, Howard R.Hoffman
  - Pres. Elliot with a group of men, a reception scene, undated (Box 3, Folder 19.5)
  - Pres. Elliot with Oliver Gasch, undated (Box 3, Folder 19.6)
  - An individual being honored, undated (Box 3, Folder 19.7)
  - General Alumni meeting, Houston, Texas, 02/12/1980 (Box 3, Folder 19.8)
    Pres. Elliot with Robert C.Bennet, Jr. and others
  - Connecticut Bar Ass. meeting, New Haven, 05/21/1980 (Box 3, Folder 19.9)
    Noren, Miane, Girsten
  - GW Law Ass. Annual Lunceon, Maryland Bar Association, 01/12/1980 (Box 3, Folder 19.1)
    Gov. Harry R. Hughes receiving the Professional Achievement Award from the Hon. Sheldon S. Cohen
  - Alumni Dinner, Boston, MA., 05/02/1980 (Box 3, Folder 19.11)
    James G. Reardon, James M. Shanon
  - Two speakers, undated (Box 3, Folder 19.12)
  - A group in gowns, undated (Box 3, Folder 19.13)
  - Annual reception honoring the Graduation Class, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.1)
    Dean Robert Kramer chatting with Ann Ashtun, David F. Bantleon, and Deedee Stokes
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.2)
    Phil Herrick, Judges Oliver Gasch, Mr. and Mrs. Ivan V. White, and Cliff Dougherty
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.3)
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.4)
    Susan and Clyde Sumida, Unidentified
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.5)
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.6)
    Unidentified group chatting
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.7)
    Phil Henrick and unidentified group
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.8)
    Susan and Clyde Lumida
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.9)
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.1)
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.11)
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.12)
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.13)
    Hank Berlinary, Mr. and Mrs. Pascal
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.14)
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.15)
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.16)
    Phil Herrick, Judge Gasch,and Mr Daugherty
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.17)
    Susan and Clyde Sumida
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.18)
    The reception table
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.19)
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.2)
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.21)
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.22)
    Unidentified groups chatting
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.23)
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.24)
    A speaker,and invitees having food and refreshment
  - Senior Reception, National Lawyers Club, 04/17/1971 (Box 3, Folder 20.25)
    Unidentified invitees having food
  - Patent Law Reception, groups chatting, 06/02/1971 (Box 3, Folder 21.1)
  - Patent Law Reception, groups chatting, 06/02/1971 (Box 3, Folder 21.2)
  - Patent Law Reception, groups chatting, 06/02/1971 (Box 3, Folder 21.3)
  - Patent Law Reception, groups chatting, 06/02/1971 (Box 3, Folder 21.4)
  - Swearing-In, Richmond, VA., 10/03/1972 (Box 3, Folder 22.1)
    Donald Stout, Mary Stout, Mike McQuade, Jayne McQuade, Glen Tiedt etc. See print for detailed listing
  - Swearing-In, Richmond, VA., 10/03/1972 (Box 3, Folder 22.2)
    Donald Stout, Mary Stout, Mike McQuuade, Jayne McQuade,Glen Tiedt etc. See print for detailed listing
  - Swearing-In, Richmond, VA., 10/03/1972 (Box 3, Folder 22.3)
    Jacqueline Bailey, William Bailey, Jayne McQuade, Mike McQuade etc. See print for detailed listing
  - Swearing-In, Richmond, VA., 10/03/1972 (Box 3, Folder 22.4)
    Mr. and Mrs. Douglas Mitchell, Thomas M. Makitrick, etc. See print for detailed listing
  - Swearing-In, Richmond, VA., 10/03/1972 (Box 3, Folder 22.5)
    Mr. and Mrs. Douglas Mitchell, Thomas M. Makitrick, etc.See print #4 for detailed listing
  - Swearing-In, Richmond, VA., 10/03/1972 (Box 3, Folder 22.6)
    Hand-written list of attendees
  - Groups at the dinning table, 10/03/1972 (Box 3, Folder 23.1)
  - Swearing-In, Virginia Bar Luncheon, John Marshal Hotel, 02/27/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.2)
    Unidentified groups
  - Swearing-In, Virginia Bar Luncheon, John Marshal Hotel, 02/27/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.3)
    James R. Wrenn, Jr.; Clifford A. Dougherty Richard Michael, Edwin Schneller, Dennis A.Dearing etc. See print for a complete listing
  - Swearing-In, Virginia Bar Luncheon, John Marshal Hotel, 02/27/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.4)
    James R. Wrenn, Jr., Clifford A.Dougherty,Richard Michael, Edwin Schneller, Dennis A.Dearing etc. See print for a complete listing
  - Swearing-In, Virginia Bar Luncheon, John Marshal Hotel, 02/27/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.5)
  - Swearing-In, Virginia Bar Luncheon, John Marshal Hotel, 02/27/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.6)
  - Swearing-In, Virginia Bar Luncheon, John Marshal Hotel, 02/27/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.7)
  - Swearing-In, Virginia Bar Luncheon, John Marshal Hotel, 02/27/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.8)
  - Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 10/03/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.9)
    George Buckwalter, Randal Edwin Wilbert, William Rhodes Chargk etc. See print for a complete listing
  - Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 10/03/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.1)
  - Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 10/03/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.11)
  - Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 10/03/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.12)
    George Buckwalter, Randal Edwin Wilbert, William Rhodes Chargk etc. See print #11 for a complete listing
  - Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 10/03/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.13)
  - Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 10/03/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.14)
  - Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 10/03/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.15)
  - Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 10/03/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.16)
  - Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 10/03/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.17)
  - Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 10/03/1973 (Box 3, Folder 23.18)
  - Swearing in Ceremony Brunch, Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 06/04/1974 (Box 3, Folder 24.1)
    Cliff Dougherty, Philip L. Radoff, Karyl S. Luck, J.H. Luck, Beverly Blondeil, James H. Blondell, Dale C. Saliba, Sallie G. Saliba
  - Swearing in Ceremony Brunch, Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 06/04/1974 (Box 3, Folder 24.2)
  - Swearing in Ceremony Brunch, Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 06/04/1974 (Box 3, Folder 24.3)
    Sheila Beam, Jembo Beam, George Ball, Carolyn Ball, Thomas Gustafson, Sarah Gustafson, Cdr. James C. Beam, Susan Beam
  - Swearing in Ceremony Brunch, Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 06/04/1974 (Box 3, Folder 24.4)
  - Swearing in Ceremony Brunch, Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 06/04/1974 (Box 3, Folder 24.5)
    Don Smith, Mrs. Ravdin, Linda Raudin N. Sam Clifton, Bill Motes, Carolyn Motes, Mrs.Smith
  - Swearing in Ceremony Brunch, Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 06/04/1974 (Box 3, Folder 24.6)
  - Swearing in Ceremony Brunch, Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 06/04/1974 (Box 3, Folder 24.7)
  - Swearing in Ceremony Brunch, Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 06/04/1974 (Box 3, Folder 24.8)
    Harold P. Deely, Matthew Low, Neil H. Kaufman, Fay L. Kaufman, Rochelle Blumenthal, David A.Blumenthal, LT. Col. Elisha K. Amos
  - Swearing in Ceremony Brunch, Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 06/04/1974 (Box 3, Folder 24.9)
  - Swearing in Ceremony Brunch, Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 06/04/1974 (Box 3, Folder 24.1)
    Larry Thomas, Jonathan Collom, Mergy Collom, Nancy Bell, Michael Bell, William L. Schmidt, Barbara L. Ardis
  - Swearing in Ceremony Brunch, Virginia Supreme Court, John Marshal Hotel, 06/04/1974 (Box 3, Folder 24.11)
  - Two Men At Dining Table, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.1)
  - President Elliot and another man chatting over lunch, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.2)
  - Daniel P. Oppenheim with other two individuals, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.3)
  - David C. Nurchism and another man, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.4)
  - A Group possing for a picture, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.5)
  - Commissioner Everett Macintyre and two other men, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.6)
  - Dr. Seymour Alpert with others, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.7)
  - John Mcintire and Prof. William Frayar with others, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.8)
  - A Couple, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.9)
  - Two Men Chatting, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.1)
  - Dean Kramer Chatting with a man, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.11)
  - Four Men Possing for a Picture, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.12)
  - A Father and a Daughter? in robes, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.13)
  - President Elliot, Dean Kramer and another person chatting, undated (Box 3, Folder 25.14)
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, Marvin Center, 10/04/1972 (Box 3, Folder 26.1)
    Laurene margolis, Henry Berliner, Mrs. L. Majolis, and Dean Kramer
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, Marvin Center, 10/04/1972 (Box 3, Folder 26.2)
    Joseph Nacrelli and Dean Robert Kramer
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, Marvin Center, 10/04/1972 (Box 3, Folder 26.3)
    Group photo
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, Marvin Center, 10/04/1972 (Box 3, Folder 26.4)
    Philip Herrick, Richard Lyon, John W. Hechinger
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, Marvin Center, 10/04/1972 (Box 3, Folder 26.5)
    Philip Herrick, Judge Harold Greene, John W. Hechinger, Marshall Gardner
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, Marvin Center, 10/04/1972 (Box 3, Folder 26.6)
    Joseph nacrelli and Dean Robert Kramer
  - 106th Founders Day GWU Center, 10/29/1971 (Box 3, Folder 27.1)
    O.S. Colelough, Sam Flickinger, Newell Ellison
  - 106th Founders Day Luncheon, 10/30/1971 (Box 3, Folder 27.2)
    Clifford A. Dougherty, David Urey, E.K. Morris, Brooks Hays, Philip Herrick
  - 106th Founders' Day, GWU Center, 10/29/1971 (Box 3, Folder 27.3)
    Dean Edward Potts, Sheldon Cohen, Philip Herrick
  - 106th Founders' Day, GWU Center, 10/29/1971 (Box 3, Folder 27.4)
    President Lloyd Elliot, Al Capp
  - 106th Founders' Day, GWU Center, 10/29/1971 (Box 3, Folder 27.5)
    Rae Ann Fichtner, Jay Fichtner, and their son Mark
  - 106th Founders' Day, GWU Center, 10/29/1971 (Box 3, Folder 27.6)
  - Jawarski, Commencement, 06/1974 (Box 3, Folder 28.1)
  - Jawarski and Weaver Commencement, 06/1974 (Box 3, Folder 28.2)
  - Jawarski and Weaver Commencement, 06/1974 (Box 3, Folder 28.3)
  - Jawarski speaking at the Commencement, 06/1974 (Box 3, Folder 28.4)
  - Jawarski speaking at the Commencement, 06/1974 (Box 3, Folder 28.5)
  - Jawarski with others at the Commencement, 06/1974 (Box 3, Folder 28.6)
  - Jawarski with others at the Commencement, 06/1974 (Box 3, Folder 28.7)
  - Judge L. Jackson Embrey, Judge Burnita Shelton Mathews, Joseph Sutherland Wright, Julius Axelrod, 06/1968 (Box 3, Folder 29.1)
  - Judge L. Jackson Embrey, Judge Burnita Shelton Mathews, Joseph Sutherland Wright, Julius Axelrod, 06/1968 (Box 3, Folder 29.2)
  - David W. Amram III, Frederick C. Beleny, Pres. Lloyd H. Elliot, Judge L. Jackson Embrey, 02/1968 (Box 3, Folder 29.3)
  - GWU Law Alumni Association, Maryland State Bar Association Midyear Mtg., 01/09/1987 (Box 3, Folder 30.1)
    Irvin Lavine
  - GWU Law Alumni Association, Maryland State Bar Association Midyear Mtg., 01/09/1987 (Box 3, Folder 30.2)
    Ass. Dean Edward Potts
  - GWU Law Alumni Association, Maryland State Bar Association Midyear Mtg., 01/09/1987 (Box 3, Folder 30.3)
    Karel Petraitis
  - GWU Law Alumni Association, Maryland State Bar Association Midyear Mtg., 01/09/1987 (Box 3, Folder 30.4)
  - GWU Law Alumni Association, Maryland State Bar Association Midyear Mtg., 01/09/1987 (Box 3, Folder 30.5)
    Ass. Dean Edward Potts presenting Professional Achievement Award to Irvin Lavine
  - GWU Law Alumni Association, Maryland State Bar Association Midyear Mtg., 01/09/1987 (Box 3, Folder 30.6)
    J. Willard Nalls Jr., Irvin Lavine, Edward Fenwick Jr., Ronald Willoner
  - GWU Law Alumni Association, Maryland State Bar Association Midyear Mtg., 01/09/1987 (Box 3, Folder 30.7)
    Matt Lavine, Sherrie Krauser, Irvin Lavine, Judge Bess lavin, and Hillary Lavine
  - GWU Law Alumni Association, Maryland State Bar Association Midyear Mtg., 01/09/1987 (Box 3, Folder 30.8)
    J. Willard Nalls Jr., Edward Fenwick, and Ronald Willoner
  - First Year Moot Court Competition, 04/23/1981 (Box 3, Folder 31.1)
    Patricia Gotsthalk, Carla Friend, Hon. John Ferren, D.C.Court of Appeals; Hon. Abner Mikva, US court of appeals for D.C. Circuit, Carol Fortine,Laura Foggan, Hon. Gerhard Gessell
  - First Year Moot Court Competition, Hon. John, 04/23/1981 (Box 3, Folder 31.2)
    Ferren, Hon. Abner Mikva, Hon. Gerhard Gesell, Associate Dean Teresa Schwartz, NLC
  - First Year Moot Court Competition, 04/23/1981 (Box 3, Folder 31.3)
  - Van Vleck Moot Court Case Club, NLC, 04/01/1982 (Box 3, Folder 31.4)
    Dean Jerome A. Barron presents the prize money checks to the 1981-82 upper class winners- J. Charles Carlson and Thomas Z. Carlson
  - D.C. Chapter, 05/19/1972 (Box 3, Folder 32.1)
    Herrick speaking, Procop, Gerner, and Ward
  - D.C. Chapter, 05/19/1972 (Box 3, Folder 32.2)
  - D.C. Chapter, 05/19/1972 (Box 3, Folder 32.3)
  - D.C. Chapter, 05/19/1972 (Box 3, Folder 32.4)
  - D.C. Chapter, 05/19/1972 (Box 3, Folder 32.5)
    Ward, George Novka and others Chatting
  - D.C. Chapter, 05/19/1972 (Box 3, Folder 32.6)
  - D.C. Chapter, 05/19/1972 (Box 3, Folder 32.7)
  - D.C. Chapter, 05/19/1972 (Box 3, Folder 32.8)
    Franklin N. Stone and Tim Bero[?]
  - 18th Conference of the Inter-American Bar Association Rio de Janerio, 08/15/1973 --08/25/1973 (Box 3, Folder 33.1)
    See print identification
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, Class of 1921, 05/14/1971 (Box 3, Folder 34.1)
    See print for identification
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, Class of 1921, 05/14/1971 (Box 3, Folder 34.2)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/11/1973 (Box 3, Folder 35.1)
    Munson H. lane, Carl A. Marshall, Edgar w. Pumphrey, Francis Moore, Samuel C. Nichols
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/11/1973 (Box 3, Folder 35.2)
    Anne Lombard Kendig, President Lloyd Elliot
  - 50th anniversary Reunion, Class of 1925, undated (Box 3, Folder 36.1)
  - 50th anniversary Reunion, Class of 1925, undated (Box 3, Folder 36.2)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, Class of 1926, 05/07/1976 (Box 3, Folder 37.1)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, Class of 1926, 05/07/1976 (Box 3, Folder 37.2)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, Class of 1926, 05/07/1976 (Box 3, Folder 37.3)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, Class of 1926, 05/07/1976 (Box 3, Folder 37.4)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, Class of 1926, 05/07/1976 (Box 3, Folder 37.5)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, Class of 1926, 05/07/1976 (Box 3, Folder 37.6)
    James J. Capello, Edwina V.A. Avery, Roger R. Kautfman
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, Class of 1926, 05/07/1976 (Box 3, Folder 37.7)
    George H. Koster, Marie Crandall Lawder, J. William Lawder, son of Marrie Crandall Lawder
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, Class of 1926, 05/07/1976 (Box 3, Folder 37.8)
    Paul M. Niebell, Mildred J. Griffin, Mrs. Niebell, Jack A. Moncure
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, Class of 1926, 05/07/1976 (Box 3, Folder 37.9)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, Class of 1926, 05/07/1976 (Box 3, Folder 37.1)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38.1)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38.2)
    [Missing]
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38.3)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38.4)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38.5)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38.6)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38.7)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38.8)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38.1)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38.11)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38.12)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38.13)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38.19)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39.1)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39.2)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39.3)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39.4)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39.5)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39.6)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39.7)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39.8)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39.9)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39.1)
  - Group of men standing, undated (Box 3, Folder 39.11)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39.12)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39.13)
  - ABA participants, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39.14)
  - Walter E. Dance, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - President Elliot, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Two men chatting over breakfast, undated (Box 4, Folder 42.1)
  - A group enjoying refreshments and chatting, undated (Box 4, Folder 42.2)
  - A group enjoying refreshments and chatting, undated (Box 4, Folder 42.3)
  - A group enjoying refreshments and chatting, undated (Box 4, Folder 42.4)
  - Two men chatting, undated (Box 4, Folder 42.5)
  - Two men chatting, undated (Box 4, Folder 42.6)
  - A group of men possing for a picture, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Dean Kramer, two men and women in an office, undated (Box 4, Folder 44.1)
  - Dean Kramer, two men and women in an office, undated (Box 4, Folder 44.2)
  - Dean Kramer, two men and women in an office, undated (Box 4, Folder 44.3)
  - Dean Kramer, two men and women in an office, undated (Box 4, Folder 44.4)
  - DC Chapter Law Alumni Luncheon, undated (Box 4, Folder 45.1)
    Hon. Patricia Roberts Harris addressing the partcipants, see print
  - DC Chapter Law Alumni Luncheon, undated (Box 4, Folder 45.2)
    E.A. Pottis addressing participants
  - DC Chapter Law Alumni Luncheon, 07/02/1971 (Box 4, Folder 45.3)
  - David Pelton Moore at his typewriter for Law Sch., 07/02/1971 (Box 4, Folder 46.1)
  - David Pelton Moore at his typewriter for Law Sch., 07/02/1971 (Box 4, Folder 46.2)
  - David Pelton Moore, 07/02/1971 (Box 4, Folder 46.3)
    High Pile Fabric Invention
  - David Pelton Moore, 07/02/1971 (Box 4, Folder 46.4)
  - David Pelton Moore, 07/02/1971 (Box 4, Folder 46.5)
  - National Law Center Advising Council Meeting, 03/24/1970 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - N.Y. State Bar, participants, undated (Box 4, Folder 48.1)
  - N.Y. State Bar, participants, undated (Box 4, Folder 48.2)
  - GWU Law Alumni Breakfast at Washington State, Portland, Oregon, undated (Box 4, Folder 49.1)
    Walter N. Fuchigamiand and Lee M. Finders
  - GWU Law Alumni Luncheon at California State Bar Meeting, San Diego,California, 09/15/1971 (Box 4, Folder 49.2)
    Charles T. Manatt, Vincent E. Sullivan, Don W. Martens
  - GWU Law Alumni Luncheon at California State Bar Meeting, San Diego,California, 09/15/1971 (Box 4, Folder 49.3)
    Two men, unidentified
  - GWU Law Alumni Breakfast at the Colorado State Bar Meeting, Colorado Springs, Colorado, 10/16/1971 (Box 4, Folder 49.4)
    President Philip F. Herrick and William E. Doyle
  - GWU Law Alumni Luncheon at California State Bar Meeting, San Diego,California, 09/15/1971 (Box 4, Folder 49.5)
    A speaker
  - GWU Law Alumni Association at Washington State, undated (Box 4, Folder 49.6)
    Unidentified group
  - Four men Chatting, undated (Box 4, Folder 49.7)
  - Group posing for a picture, undated (Box 4, Folder 49.8)
  - GWU Law Alumni Breakfast at Colorado State Bar meeting, undated (Box 4, Folder 49.9)
    George H. Whitcomb, Ernest Hugh Sandouval, Carlos F. Lucero
  - GWU Law Alumni Luncheon at the Texas State Bar meeting, Dallas, Texas, undated (Box 4, Folder 50.1)
    Rae Ann Fichtner, Cliff Dougherty, and the Hon. Sarah T. Hughes
  - GWU Alumni Dinner, University Club, Salt Lake City, Utah, undated (Box 4, Folder 50.2)
    Mrs. M. Byron Fisher and the Hon. Vernon Ronney Jr
  - GWU Law Alumni meeting, St. Petersburg, Florida, 10/02/1971 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    John A. Hanley III, Hon. Mildred Reeves Sherman, and William M. Hobby